*This video is provided by a staff member.
*Provided by staff.
*Served by the staff.
*Standing.
Like a special life house.
I see.
Punch.
Wrap it around a reverse direct hit.
What should I do, dissolve it into sludge in water ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
We're here at Fukuoka Prefecture's Murokata Clan, it's Murakata.
Long time no see.
Remember me?
Yamada-san.
No, not at all.
Not at all.
I'm Riko Ueda.
And they're all here.
That's right.
Probably at the second Goo Goo house.
You know...
Cooking.
From 12:00.
Since then...
I don't know. It's like we're still new members.
How long ago was that?
Three years.
You said you were in eighth grade.
I was in eighth grade.
And now, by the way?
I'm in the first grade.
You're a freshman!
That's right. It's been that long.
Long time no see, Murakami-san.
It's been four years.
It's been about 4 years.
That long?
How's it going? How's Murakata?
He went by boat, but couldn't make it... so he came back.
Oh no...
Did you get out of there?
That was the last one.
It's a beautiful day.
Where are we?
This is a place of culture and inspiration.
Murakata Yuriks.
You're here for the first time.
It's my first time.
It's quite a big facility, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
There's a hall.
There's a general merchandise hall.
And there's also a lawn, a library, and then there's a lawn.
Yes, it is. That's right.
Do you also hold various events here in Nakata?
Before the Batten Show itself became the Batten Show itself, we were a few generations old.
We were a few generations ago, and our first stage was here.
Is there such a big hall?
Yes, it is.
Momokura-chan, one of my seniors, was the opening act for a live viewing.
I also had the opportunity to visit them for a public radio recording.
So it's a place that you have a close relationship with.
Yes, that's right.
That's why I invited you here today.
Thank you.
What are you doing? Well...
We don't know.
There's an important announcement we don't know about.
We don't know that either, so we'd like to ask him.
I'm so surprised that Mr. Hamada is making the announcement.
There was a teenage announcement and then a teenage announcement? He's dressed so casually...
I'm dressed like a teenager.
That's a staff T-shirt from last year.
Oh, yeah!
Mr. Bussey's name is on it, too.
What kind of announcement is Mr. Hamada making?
Let's get right to it!
The Chest Shoulder Festival 2023 will be held again this year!
Oh!
Chest and Shoulders Festival!
It's not a festival!
Oh, thank goodness! Hey, guys! It's not a festival? It was a festival!
The T-shirt you're wearing is for the Murakata festival, right? Yes, it is. Last year we held the Chest Shoulder Festival for the past 10 years.
We've done a lot of social contribution and environmental activities mainly through music festivals.
Now we are going to do it the other way around.
Reverse it?
In the big crown of the chest and shoulders size, the music festival will remain as the chest and shoulders festival, and we will do E-sports.
E-sports and other various activities.
We're going to do it.
So it's a big expansion.
It's like a big composite event.
That's wonderful.
I heard that it's been decided.
Have you set a date for the event?
November 3, 4 and 5.
Three days!
It's going to be a big event!
And that's in less than two months!
That's right.
You were there, weren't you? Yes, I was in it last year.
It was held in June last year.
I don't know how it went.
But it was amazing.
I don't know.
I got the impression that it was very spacious.
It was a lot of fun.
The venue was a stage.
The place
It's spacious.
The green, the sky, and the nice feeling of the stage? The place? It's spacious. Green and sky.
A pleasant stage. I'm not wrong.
It was my first time at a big festival, so it was fun to be there and to experience the atmosphere of a festival.
But it was raining really hard.
What?
The rain.
The difference between the green and the sky.
It was a lie!
It was like, "Oh, my God!
It's like it's sunny. It's a great summer festival.
It wasn't sunny when we were on stage.
Miraculously.
It was sunny then.
Overall, the rain was
A little bit on the second day pretty much.
Oh, I see.
Coppaley.
I don't want to show you that footage.
I don't want to show it to you.
On the contrary, I want to see it. .... If you said something about it being cooler, did they do it inside? They had the music festival inside and a lot of events on the lawn.
So there's a lawn area?
Why the Yurix Murakata?
Certainly.
That's the thing.
It's kind of...
Ew!
No, I'm afraid to be official.
Scary, scary.
No, it's not...
Originally, it was a Murakata festival, so it was done by Murakata.
But then we got requests from various places to hold it at our place.
So we held it in Fukutsu, and then in Kitakyushu City.
Last year was the 10th festival, and we originally thought we'd stop after 10, so we started from the beginning.
Oh well...
That's what I was thinking.
But if we can do something like the Murakata Festival
I thought, "If we can do something like the Murakata Festival, let's do it all over again from scratch.
If that's the case, I'd like to do it in Murakata.
I see.
So it's like a renewal, or a new beginning.
That's right.
Wow.
And this time it's not a music festival, but a breast-shaped festival.
We had a lot of help from you last year.
Mr. Bathe...
I'd like you to come up with more ideas for this year's festival, in more ways than one.
Ideas? I see!
Then you can join us, Mr. Fujimoto.
Well, I can only give you about 5 or 10 minutes of material.
What? You're going to do it?
I mean, what can you do? I don't know where it is.
I'm going to show it to you later.
Well, maybe you can do something like this.
I see. Well, I'm sure they'll get excited when they see it.
And if you look at them, you can get ideas, and you can talk about it and create fun things, and have fun ideas.
I'll be happy to cooperate with you in that regard.
Yes, that's right. I will cooperate with you. I will cooperate with you. I will be happy to cooperate with you.
In Murokura City, is Aichan used in a normal way?
Yes, during summer vacations, at the library, and at the Society.
It is a place where all citizens gather.
There was also a gym.
They have a gym?
Yes, I went to the gym.
There was a gym. I used to go to the gym. Wow.
Wow, it's a big place. Is it a lobby?
It's very spacious. The lobby is huge.
What is this place? Is it usually called a place for relaxation?
A place for relaxation.
We have an event hall and a main hall.
For events, it's the main hall,
The ConzaFest is in the Main Hall.
The event hall is in the main hall.
There is also a store.
Snacks and other things.
Rumne (soda pop).
It's more substantial than I thought it would be.
Indeed. There is a good variety of food.
Among them, the one that you can relax in is
I think it's a pretty big hall.
Oh! It's huge!
It's huge! Oh, my God! It's huge! Big!
Oh, my God!
You got it, didn't you?
Did you do it here? We did.
Oh, but it's here!
Right here!
He was right behind us!
Oh, my God!
Here!
This is huge!
Oh, my God!
It's so big! It echoes!
There's like second floor seating.
It looks a bit like a gymnasium, but there are speakers on top, so it's really big! It's like a gymnasium, but it's got speakers on top, so it's really big!
It looks a little like a gymnasium, but there are speakers on top, so it's really loud!
It really is! This place looks like a gymnasium!
It's huge!
It's a huge event!
This is amazing!
On the day of the event, we'll have seats on the floor and everything will be standing.
It will be like a special live house!
I see.
I'm sure we'll get a place for this. We'll do it here like Hearth. .... I was wondering if I'd be on the audience side, so I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's a nice hall, isn't it?
I usually do concerts.
We also have gymnastic competitions here.
It can also be used as a gymnasium.
So we can have athletic meets here.
Yes, we can.
We can have athletic meets, but do we have athletic meets?
It's fall. We can have a land ball. .... This is totally different... it's like a stage for a festival... with vision...
I'm sure it's not a gymnasium.
It's not a gymnasium.
How many people can this hold?
It's not that big, is it?
Thousands, right?
It's bigger than ZEPP, right?
Bigger.
Not even close.
What's it going to hold, 4,000 people?
Three thousand four thousand.
That's great.
I'd like you to see the line up.
It's a big place.
You're pushing it...
It's so surreal!
Here we go.
It's so big. ...... Is this a stand? This is a stand.
Does this mean this is a staircase? That's nice.
But you can certainly see a lot more people behind you if you stand on something like that,
It's very close.
Very close.
It's a lot of pressure.
Indeed.
It's amazing.
What do you sing? I don't know. Wow, that's a lot of pressure. Yes, it is. That's great.
What do you want to sing? What are you going to sing?
I don't know.
This song.
It's good. Yes, it is.
I'll be right there with you. I want to dance with you.
I was going to put it in.
We'll go upstairs, too.
The second floor too?
That's great.
It feels so close.
It's nice.
Yeah, it feels close.
It's true.
I don't think I've ever done a standing concert.
First time.
That's great.
In a show like this, you play a few songs, right?
How do you decide?
I listen to the songs of the artists I'm going to perform with, and I think these songs will be the ones that stick.
I think it's a good balance.
I'm glad to hear that.
That's how they think about it.
You're going to play, right? Are you sure?
I thought about it a lot, but I don't think it'll come out.
It's so rare to hear something like that.
I'm glad to hear that.
So I can't say that I'm going to play this song at this stage, but I think I have a clear idea of what I want to do.
But after singing it today, I think I have a clear image of what I want to do,
So this is a little more promising.
I will do my best.
October Announcement
The sun is shining.
The sun is coming out very well.
It's not so bad.
The lingering summer heat.
I wonder what the temperature is in November.
I wonder if I can wear a T-shirt.
Oh, sickle-cutter.
Uh, sickle-cutter.
Oh, I can't do it.
I'm the only one on location this time.
Uh-oh.
I don't know. I just got that feeling.
That's great!
I had that feeling, you know, like I'm looking for a habit.
It's so big!
Let's have an insect booth.
I know...
Insect wrestling with a shivabu.
Insect wrestling.
It's something to do in the summer.
But we'll also have fall bugs.
Tsetse bugs, crickets...
Let's get the insects out.
You write about swimming pools, and korobi, and korobi, will you eat them? Let's get the insects out. Let's get the insects out.
It says something about a swimming pool.
Do you have a swimming pool in the summer?
They only do it in the summer now.
I'd love to go back.
I want to go back.
That's great.
Kamal.
We'll go to the festival here too.
Kohunkongkohun... this is a burial mound.
It's a tomb!
Then it's no good.
People will get mad at me.
They'll be pissed off.
It's magnificent.
It's nice.
It's like a game world.
I'd love to have my picture taken in a place like this.
Or artists.
It would be nice if they made a photo spot here.
That's nice.
Like a cosplay plaza.
I want to go through the archway
I want to go through the archway.
That's nice.
It's true.
I'm sure it'll come to you.
It's real.
I want to be in a cute festival!
And the Dragon Ball comedians.
It's the most comfortable time since November.
Easier to spend time with.
I'm wearing a lot of stuff.
And looking good, too.
Yes, it's perfect.
It's the best for professionals.
Or this stone object.
And this... Look.
If you take a big sword...
If you take it, something will grow.
Maybe...
If you do something, you know...
This is what I see.
Wow!
It's so beautiful.
It's a huge lawn.
It's so much bigger than I thought it would be.
Oh, this is water!
Is that what this pool is?
No!
Is it a flushing pool?
Floating pool
Floating pool.
It's huge!
Wow, it's really big!
It's amazing!
I want to go in! Wow, it's huge! - It's huge. It's huge! - I want to go in. I want to go in.
- Wow, it's huge!
- It's so nice!
- It really looks like an outdoor festival venue.
- It's like some kind of outdoor event, free and open to the public, where families can play and have fun for the whole day.
- Wow!
- So it's more like a food and beverage booth.
- Yes, that's right.
- You should have one.
I want vegetables.
It's small, but we can set up a stage.
Oh.
Various things...
A mini live show...
That sounds great.
Something like that.
You know, fluffy...
Smell...
Oh, I see.
Smells like fluff.
Like a trampoline.
You know what?
I love that one.
Oh...
That's right, that's right.
Like, out and stuff.
I see.
Sounds fun.
Now I'm thinking... there's a mountain there, right?
Yes.
I was thinking we could shoot fireworks from there.
Isn't it great?
It would be great.
I'm thinking about it.
At night.
It'd be great.
That's true, but there's no fireworks in Nonakada.
That's right... there are no fireworks shows.
Like fireworks.
No!
There's no place to see them like this.
Across the sea or on the river...
It's a little far away.
So to see the fireworks in such a realistic place
It's so nice!
I love it!
It's great!
I wonder what kind of food and drink booths would be good.
Something like this.
Wow.
Yup.
Oh, fall sweet potatoes!
I'm sorry.
I love sweet potatoes.
Sweet potatoes?
I know, but...
Sweet potatoes and baked sweet potatoes.
A baked sweet potato.
That's nice.
If you're going to go that far, why not go to Kyushu?
Kagoshima.
Aira.
Yes.
Oh, there's something like a truck.
You know, you can swap out the stickers, like a truck.
to match the truck
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
And I wonder if there will be some kind of sister media of that Goo Goo Goo, Yuji's, that I want to eat.
Oh! Spoon pot?
A little early
Oh, that's nice, all lined up like this.
I love it!
I wonder if we'll get
I wonder if Kakuda's Tenshindon will be there.
Yes.
That attraction too...
I want to ride that!
I want to ride that one!
I want to go on that lawn tour.
We'd like to put about 15,000 people in here.
I'd like you all to think about how to make it fun.
I'd like everyone to think about it.
Right here.
I see.
We'll get 15,000 people in here.
We'll make a contraption.
Let's see what we can do.
The stage is right here.
It's pretty big.
It's just this wide.
The stage is pretty solid, and it's just this wide.
It's pretty solid.
I hope this gives you some ideas.
Can we do a live broadcast?
Live here?
Yeah.
What do you do?
We could do a live broadcast.
Maybe we could do some kind of a participatory thing or something.
Bingo games, bingo.
Quiz night.
Maybe even a comedy act.
Comedy?
Is it too tight?
No, I just think it's big.
Big?
I mean, it's big.
I mean, it's like a big, thick cloud...
What's up?
Dokudokshu.
I've seen it in Chinese.
It's like a magic show.
Boo-boo, magic.
It's hard to do when you can see it from the front of the school.
I don't understand Chinese... is DocDocShow in Chinese? I don't know Chinese.
I don't know the name.
Maybe it's Chinese.
I don't know, maybe it's Chinese.
That's good.
It's like exercise.
Yeah, sure.
What about your dog?
It's a fetch doggie grand prix.
I'm proud of my dog.
You know, something with animals.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Personally, I'd like to...
Let's release a big elephant tortoise or something.
Ha-ha-ha.
And give them some chimaeras.
Here?
It's a great place to interact with people.
Is it dangerous to use a drone?
I don't know. It's not a drone experience.
Can I ask you something?
Do you want to make a character or something?
I don't know.
Yeah, sure.
Like the 35th anniversary.
Oh!
Thank you.
At school.
Fireworks, too... like this at the end.
You put it under the paper... and then you put it under the paper... and then you put it under the paper... and then you put it under the paper.
I'll take it up
I'm sure it'll make you hungry and happy...
I'm sure it'll be a real restaurant.
I'm sure they'll love it!
That's for sure!
Maybe we could do an online launch.
And decide who comes out on top.
Gourmet One Grand Prix.
I'm sure we'd have a lot of fun talking about it.
I'm sure we can come up with a lot of ideas.
It's a little hot at this point, with all the glare.
I'm at my limit.
I'm at my wits' end. Oh, watering can? Oh, watering can?
Oh, watering can?
Ah, watering?
Oh, watering can? Oh, you don't have water, you know, like ants, you know, in there, yes, sir.
It's not a water spinner. What's his name?
Not a coinworm. I don't remember what it is.
We need a bug lady.
Oh, sorry, personal.
It's personal.
They're really looking for bugs out of habit.
You like bugs?
I've always liked them.
I don't know...
It's hard for girls to understand.
It's hard for girls to understand anything.
That's right.
Anything.
Look, dragonflies are laying eggs right now.
Oh, they're laying eggs. They're laying eggs.
They're laying eggs.
They're laying eggs?
And they're laying eggs.
Oh, I see.
Red dragonfly
This, maybe a territorial salty dragonfly is a salty dragonfly! This one, maybe a territorial salty dragonfly coming in.
The blue one
This is the salty dragonfly
Oh, but that one
The one they're chasing around.
A man and a woman.
You don't use these things.
Either one of them.
Insects locke
All of them, now.
InsectsLockeYes, so I said yes, and it was a little bit hot, so we moved to a cooler place.
We talked a lot on the lawn earlier, and I think we came up with a few ideas.
How was it, Kanda-san?
Suddenly
As for this event...
If Gugoo is going to enter this event...
Are you sure you're okay with such a low profile?
Excuse me! Center!
If Goo Goo is going to be in this event...
I don't want to just sit on your chest and shoulders.
For example, you could be a Kyushu bed student...
or a student of KURUBE...
We would like to be involved with students from various places, such as students from KURUBE, students from Kusahara, and so on.
And then there are the students in the steppe. We had students from Kusahara.
I wanted to make it a project where we could interact with various people.
Oh!
I knew that Mr. Haruno had met with APU students from BEP before.
Big!
I'd like to have Mr. Haruno visit with the APU students at BEP.
And APU students have actually already talked about this too.
Oh!
I'm so glad you said you wanted to participate.
I'm so happy! I thought it would be great if we could do something like this, but we've already talked about it, and they said they wanted to participate.
I thought it's so nice that he said he wanted to join us.
We'll bring Bep's hot springs and use them as a footbath.
You can do that?
What?
Can you bring hot water?
Student's flash idea
A narrow storehouse.
I put it there.
About 200 kilometers.
We talked about having a festival of about 200 kilos with the students.
I think it would be great if we could really make that happen.
I'd like to go talk about it again.
Boo-boo!
Boo boo!
Go to Goo Goo Goo, go to Goo Goo Goo God, that's good!
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a ticket to the shrine.
I'm sure it's hard for the kids to go to the shrine.
That's how religions arise, right?
Let's put something like "ana" on the wall... and show it from a fixed point camera...
You can show it on Youtube or something.
And the viewers can comment on it.
And the viewers comment on it.
That's right.
That's good.
Does a hungry mind bring any good?
Sure of what? Nothing.
Nothing... nothing... but everything... everything intersects.
Four years ago on location I got power from the Breast-shaped Shrine.
I did inject it. It's true... it's like having a new Nakata Shrine again.
It's that good!
Can't we make a bigger one?
Like a yuru-kyara?
You could even take pictures of it.
That's a good idea.
How big?
Big enough to hold a person.
About the same size?
About the size of a fluffball.
That's great.
And since you mentioned fireworks.
I just checked while I was on my way.
We're going to make fireworks that everyone can make together.
Fireworks?
Fireworks.
You can make fireworks?
I want to.
What do you mean you can make fireworks?
What are you gonna make?
What do you think?
What are you going to make?
What are you going to make? What do you mean?
What?
If it's okay with you, you can go now and...
Plan your vote.
Plan the vote. Make it a test run.
You can make a test run like that?
Yeah, it's pretty much a go.
That's so cool.
Maybe we could even try it out.
Test drive?
Are you giving it a try?
I don't know if that's possible, but...
But here it is, just in case.
That's great!
That's really good!
Let's go.
I'll get over it.
If you can make fireworks...
I'd love to.
I'm nervous.
I'll be waiting.
What are you working on? ...... Thank you! Here you go.
Here you go. - Thank you.
Bye-bye.
What a waste we have collected so far this year!
Plastic bottle trash
Plus, just in case it's possible
PET bottle trash from all over the country
I'd like to make a picture book out of them.
and make a picture book out of them.
picture book?
Mr. Hamaura used it this time.
A big picture book?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, they're just regular-sized
We recycle plastic bottles and use them as paper.
I'd like to make it into a book that hopefully protects the environment.
I hope there will be flowers too.
I thought you were going to make it by sticking the lids on.
If you could force me to make it with great care.
I'll put it on paper.
I heard that the finished product will be distributed to children in countries other than Japan.
That would be wonderful.
It would be nice if you could expand the meaning of the book and make it available to the world.
I'd like to make the design of the picture book, or the content of the book itself, together with everyone.
I'd like to ask you all to create the contents of the picture book itself.
Oh, really?
Is it amazing?
Really?
It's my first time.
And, well, of course, we can't do it ourselves.
We've been working with...
I've been helping with environmental initiatives like this since 2018.
We've been helping with these environmental initiatives since 2018.
Teijin Frontier, who has been helping us with these environmental initiatives since 2018, is here today.
Oh, wow!
That's a lot of people!
Finally, we're going to do it!
Someone very persuasive is here.
My name is Yamagata from Teijin Frontier. Pleased to meet you.
Teijin Frontier is a company called Teijin, which has the ability to manufacture textile products and to connect them to the market and customers.
We have been selling products made from recycled plastic bottles since 1995.
That's amazing.
I'd like to talk a little bit about what you can do with recycled textiles,
I have some specific products to show you today,
I would like to ask you to bring your own product.
This?
It looks a little different from what I imagined.
What is it?
It's amazing.
A blanket? Is this it?
That's a blanket.
Oh, my God.
Stainless steel is amazing!
It's just a piece of cloth.
It's not cloth, it's just a normal pair of pants.
Looks like it's easy to move around in.
This is artificial leather used for shoes.
Which side?
This is the fur part.
Fur!
What?
Is this a plastic bottle?
I don't know. Is it a plastic bottle? Is this from a plastic bottle?
From a plastic bottle?
Is it a regular Force?
Yes, sir.
That's great.
And there's the rest.
You can make a character with this, can't you?
Oh, wow.
You can do it!
Made out of plastic bottles!
That's amazing.
This is a business card.
Business cards, too?
This paper is also recycled from plastic bottles.
They can make picture books out of it.
You can make picture books out of this paper?
Yes, that's right.
We need to think about paper for picture books again.
Is this kind of paper made at Sadato?
We sell the fibers used to make the paper,
We sell the fibers that make the paper, and the company that makes the paper processes the fibers,
Here in Kyushu, for example, we have Nakamura Paper Mfg,
I am in charge of sales,
They can also make paper using polyester.
They sell this type of polyester.
If you dissolve it in water and scoop it with a fine mesh, you can produce paper that looks like Japanese paper. Wow. You can make flat ittoku paper in this way,
If you change this recipe in various ways, you can make various kinds of paper,
As I mentioned earlier, it can be made into various kinds of paper.
The quality changes.
Wow.
So this is the original.
I guess that's how it is with ordinary recipes.
You can visit us for a tour.
Do you want to?
I'm going.
Oh, you want to go see it?
You want to go?
Now? Stop, stop, stop, stop, okay, it's not that far, is it? Do you want to go? You want to see the news? Do you want to go?
Now?
Is it not too far?
Yes, it is.
Yeah, but what are we going to do? You mean there will be fireworks, right?
That's right.
Can we go?
We're going to the fireworks now, and then we're going to the beach.
You want to go?
Which one?
Let's split up.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Aah! It's so hard!
Still mixed with the hair you imagine
Dissolving in water.
Oh, my gosh!
I put shampoo in it!
I did put shampoo in it, and this is what I'm talking about when I talk about PET bottle recycling in Japan!
Plastic Bottle Recycling Company
Good afternoon
Good afternoon.
We are from Kitakyushu city.
We recycle PET bottles.
We are a company called Nishinippon PET Bottle Recycling Co.
Our company recycles PET bottles.
We recycle PET bottles and ship them to our customers
We ship our products to customers who recycle them.
We ship PET bottles to customers who recycle them into products such as these.
I first produce the PET bottles as flails and then as pellets.
First of all, I manufacture them.
I manufacture the food trays and other food products here.
I am also in charge of converting them into PET bottles.
How to make PET bottles
First of all, I would like to ask everyone to remove the cap from the PET bottle when you finish drinking it.
Please distribute the caps to another plastic bottle.
The PET bottles usually have labels on them, so please remove the labels.
Please remove the labels.
Please take it off firmly.
Please rinse them lightly with water.
When the contents are gone
Before you take it out
You can crush it lightly with your foot.
In this way.
Oh, my.
That's about right.
It went pretty far, though.
If you can crush them lightly and put them out in this condition, it will make it much easier for us to recycle them,
We would appreciate your cooperation.
Also, please note that many of the items have names written on them with magic markers.
If you write your name on the body with an oil-based marker, it will be difficult to recycle that part.
It becomes something that cannot be recycled.
So, if you would like to put it out in this transparent state without your name written on it, is it OK if it is the lid?
Please write on the lids.
You can write on the lid.
You write on the lids a lot, guys.
Thank you for your cooperation in making good recycling practices!
Please cooperate with our environmental activities!
Thank you very much!
Next time notice
Thank you for all your ideas today!
Thank you very much.
You are an amazing person, aren't you?
You've come up with so many concrete ideas.
That was great!
Music, ISD, even G-ZU.
But we are limited in what we can think about.
Artists' ideas are so innovative.
I see.
It's really helpful.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I hope we can execute some of them.
I want to realize all of them.
I want to make it all happen.
Insect wrestling.
Let's all work together to make Murata-san fun.
Yes, I'll do my best!